[
  {
    "id": "434",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An EC2 instance and its mounted EBS volumes must be what?",
      "answers": [
        "in the same AZ",
        "in any AZ in the same region",
        "in any region"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["in the same AZ"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "435",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "You can upgrade an EBS volume by changing which of these?",
      "answers": [
        "change its type",
        "change its size",
        "change its location",
        "change its volume id"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["change its type", "change its size"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "436",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You can upgrade an EBS volume with no downtime?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "437",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 4",
      "question": "Which EBS volume types can you modify?",
      "answers": [
        "Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)",
        "Cold HDD (SC1)",
        "Provisioned IOPS SSD (IO1)",
        "General Purpose SSD (GP2)",
        "Magnetic"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)", "Cold HDD (SC1)", "Provisioned IOPS SSD (IO1)", "General Purpose SSD (GP2)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "438",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EBS volume type cannot be modified?",
      "answers": [
        "Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)",
        "Cold HDD (SC1)",
        "Provisioned IOPS SSD (IO1)",
        "General Purpose SSD (GP2)",
        "Magnetic"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Magnetic"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "439",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You can only modify a General Purpose SSD (GP2) to which other type of EBS volume?",
      "answers": [
        "Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)",
        "Cold HDD (SC1)",
        "Provisioned IOPS SSD (IO1)",
        "General Purpose SSD (GP2)",
        "Magnetic"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Provisioned IOPS SSD (IO1)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "440",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "From your existing volume, how do you create a new volume in another AZ in the same region?",
      "answers": [
        "take a snapshot of the volume, then select the snapshot and create a new volume from it in a new AZ in the same region",
        "take a snapshot of the volume, then copy the snapshot to the new AZ in the same region",
        "select the volume and move it to the new AZ in the same region",
        "you can't move a volume to a new AZ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["take a snapshot of the volume, then select the snapshot and create a new volume from it in a new AZ in the same region"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "441",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "From your existing volume, how do you create a new volume in another AZ in any region in the world?",
      "answers": [
        "take a snapshot of the volume, then select the snapshot and copy it to a new AZ in any region in the world",
        "take a snapshot of the volume, then select the snapshot and create a new volume from it in a new AZ in any region in the world",
        "select the volume and move it to the new AZ in any region in the world",
        "you can't move a volume to a new AZ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["take a snapshot of the volume, then select the snapshot and copy it to a new AZ in any region in the world"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "442",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "How do you move an EC2 instance to a new AZ or region?",
      "answers": [
        "take a snapshot of the root volume, create an image (AMI) of the snapshot, then copy the AMI to the region/AZ to which you wish to move the EC2 instance",
        "take a snapshot of the volume, then select the snapshot and create a new volume from it in a new AZ in any region in the world",
        "select the volume and move it to the new AZ in any region in the world",
        "you can't move an EC2 instance to a new AZ",
        "select the EC2 instance, then create an image (AMI) of the EC2 instance, then select the AMI and launch it in a new AZ in any region in the world"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["take a snapshot of the root volume, create an image (AMI) of the snapshot, then copy the AMI to the region/AZ to which you wish to move the EC2 instance"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "443",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "How do you move an EC2 instance to a new AZ within its region?",
      "answers": [
        "take a snapshot of the volume, then select the snapshot and create a new volume from it in a new AZ",
        "select the volume and move it to the new AZ",
        "you can't move an EC2 instance to a new AZ",
        "select the EC2 instance, then create an image (AMI) of the EC2 instance, then select the AMI and launch it in the new AZ by selecting a new subnet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["select the EC2 instance, then create an image (AMI) of the EC2 instance, then select the AMI and launch it in the new AZ by selecting a new subnet"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "444",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of these are for creating backups?",
      "answers": [
        "EBS volume snapshots",
        "EBS volume sourced images (AMIs)",
        "EC2 instance sourced images (AMIs)",
        "EBS volume copies"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["EBS volume snapshots"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "445",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of these are for creating new EC2 instances?",
      "answers": [
        "EBS volume snapshots",
        "images (AMIs)",
        "EBS volume copies"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["images (AMIs)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "446",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When you launch your new EC2 instance from an AMI, how do you choose the AZ in which to run it?",
      "answers": [
        "select the AZ from the subnet selection list on the console launch page",
        "you can't select a new AZ, it has to run in the same AZ as its source",
        "you select the AZ after it has launched"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["select the AZ from the subnet selection list on the console launch page"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "447",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "How do you move your EC2 instance to another region?",
      "answers": [
        "create an AMI from it, then copy the AMI to the region in which you wish to launch the EC2 instance",
        "create a snapshot of the root volume, then launch the EC2 image from the snapshot in the region in which you wish to run the EC2 instance",
        "you can't move an EC2 instance to another region"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["create an AMI from it, then copy the AMI to the region in which you wish to launch the EC2 instance"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "448",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An EBS volume is a _____?",
      "answers": [
        "a virtual hard disk",
        "a physical hard disk",
        "an array of physical hard disks",
        "a hard disk directly connected to your EC2 instance"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["a virtual hard disk"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "449",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "EBS snapshots are stored where?",
      "answers": [
        "on S3",
        "on physical disks attached to your EC2 instance",
        "on tape backup",
        "in cache memory"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["on S3"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "450",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "EBS snapshots are ________?",
      "answers": [
        "point in time copies of EBS volumes",
        "exact copies of the full EBS volume",
        "always a full copy of all of the EBS volume",
        "pointers to the EBS volume"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["point in time copies of EBS volumes"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "451",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Snapshots are stored incrementally, only the blocks that have changed since the last snapshot are moved to S3?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "452",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You MUST stop your EC2 instance before taking a snapshot of its root EBS volume?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["false"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "453",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You SHOULD stop your EC2 instance before taking a snapshot of its root EBS volume?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "454",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You CAN take a snapshot of an EC2 instance's root EBS volume while the instance is running?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "455",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "You can create AMIs from which?",
      "answers": [
        "EC2 instances",
        "EBS snapshots",
        "EBS volumes"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["EC2 instances", "EBS snapshots"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "456",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You cannot change EBS volumes on the fly?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["false"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "457",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "EBS volumes can be in a different AZ than their EC2 instance?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["false"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "458",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Snapshots of encrypted volumes are encrypted automatically?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "459",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "EBS volumes restored from encrypted snapshots are not encrypted automatically?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["false"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "460",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You can share encrypted EBS snapshots?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["false"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "461",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You can make an encrypted EBS snapshot public?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["false"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "462",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You cannot share unencrypted EBS snapshots with other AWS accounts?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["false"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "463",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You can make unencrypted EBS snapshots public?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  }
]
